(Sheldon:)Oh, God. Don't make it
so hard on her.
(Sheldon:)Look, the first someone
is the deceitful you.
(Sheldon:)The second someone
(Sheldon:)is the delightful
Dr. Lorvis.
(Penny:)Oh, this is very embarrassing.
(Penny:)Dr. Lorvis, I am so sorry.
(Penny:)I did not mean to lead you on.
(Dr Lorvis:)You touched my arm
for two Mississippis.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)That's why you were
mumbling "Mississippi."
(Leonard:)Can we talk in private?
(Penny:)Please, yes.
(Leonard:)I'll be right back.
(Sheldon:)So what other
(Sheldon:)celebrity genitalia
have you handled?
(Leonard:)So, uh, what's the deal?
(Leonard:)You take off your ring
when you go to work?
What? No! No!
(Penny:)I just put it
on the other hand and...
(Penny:)turn it around.
(Penny:)Keep that hand in my pocket.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Penny:)Well, what do you mean why?
(Penny:)Look, I make more sales
(Penny:)if these doctors
think I'm single.
(Penny:)I did the same kind of
thing as a waitress.
(Penny:)The real question is, what is
he doing in your apartment?
(Leonard:)Oh, he was upset.
(Leonard:)So Sheldon invited him
in for a hot beverage.